We've already had 40 minutes,
so we learn that this is a secret,
how to close the class with
open eyes,
okay Peter Hoenen, do you find this
training? The people who have
n't done this teacher training yet will
sleep, but the real teachers
look like this. Was that great? What do
the very advanced teachers do?
Nowhere, the clinics, then also
simultaneously, about every five minutes.
Then they really come, foreign
companies will.
This is a very high praise for a
teacher's ability. We
could practice tomorrow or make up for it today.
I'm going to go to the homework now, that's
clear. I would teach these classics
traditionally.
I won't just give
homework, a class really in the
old way, just for fun.
I always approach the class, look at it,
and thought to myself, I would like to teach in
this way. It probably takes
a
whole evening today. I
promised to do that tomorrow, but I just
like
teaching [music] in the old way.
This is a very famous part from the
three basic basements. You have your
own  Mistakes in the homework are
justified. You all have to do it with your
own regulations. This is a
very important opening ceremony.
I will tell you the first line says
I will teach you the most important things about
Buddhism. Promote the second island
where that has what the third line says.
I will help you.
You're making me really poor in Münster. It
's supervised. On the table are
many rivers. Win because there's a lot of
snow and they have no bridges because
they don't have a lake. But you had to
find the flat part to cross with.
12 to cross
the river and that
means it's a very good
place to cross the river.
Papa calls his own book. This is
the entrance to the crossing, the
entry point for people who want to take good
cadre measures
and for people who
want to achieve enlightenment. They place so much value on this.
This is Kesha Lothar's real name.
Impressed,
we had it yesterday. My studio, then
he says that's my name and Lobsang. Days, the one who
seeks freedom, the
pure spirit. Lobsang, where does the name come from?  Did he
take over the first part of Harry Potter's name because he gets a lucky shipping opportunity in an
ordinary tragicomic day, especially for
the Islamic nation?
Many people will come,
two-year-olds say they would become
Tibetan, and it's a good way.
We have three originals looking for us. We
have three teams for twelve years. The
originals, and I believe they have
n't yet gone through 100 books
because it's very difficult to find a
trio for the government in the
Tibetan language, Sanskrit books, the
300,000 books, and each of the books is unique. There is no one
above another. All the books
are wonderfully beautiful. It is the
most wonderful spiritual literature council
function in the world.
People ask, they say they would like to learn
Tibetan. Great things learn
this book by heart. You have to be able to recite it
in 203 minutes.
So if he is interested in
learning ethically, then first learn
the prayers, and then this is
extremely agile. It's simply 14.
I started with Nick like this, and that's how he started.
He now speaks pretty much entirely with the
Tibetan plan. In your
mind, Jenny is also coming. Visiting
program.
You can all come. We also have
secondary translators who translate English,
Spanish, Mandarin, German,
Russian, Arabic, and
French.
It's really difficult to teach for six
hours a day,
but your mind will grow,
and then you can teach like this. I'm
not going to Wilhelmsdorf now.
He has all of this in his mind, and it will grow.
His head has
already grown.
I give him a lot of pride so that I can
then break the last dams.
I will try my best to explain the
essence of Buddhist teachings.
The ball is great because
I will write three lines, so more. As good
as I can be as a forester, I can be as
good as it gets. I'm just a
small domino,
and that's how you usually start a book.
You can bus climb onto the throne and
bushes teach
the mental functions. Also,
traditionally,
I have more negative emotions than
anyone else in this room.
Thank you.  That you let me teach, thank you
for teaching me, and it's fun
to teach.
Thank you for letting me do this.
I do it as best I can. And
forget, if he's a teacher,
it could be that every student
is a butter and he's just trying to
bring church, not teach Buddhism.
If you say no 10,000 times,
then he'll understand. Maybe it doesn't look
so brutally moderate. Then
I just said, "I'm not a
butter." Thank you for letting me, and
I say, "This is the visitor." What
else happens? That you make the commitment.
That's a commissioner between
promises, and that's one of the most
serious promises a good person can make.
I will teach this class.
I will get you to do the same yoga
poses.
That's a promise. That's the
promise as Buddhists. You will
undertake your own students this year. And
he says, "I will not stop." Evasive clause: There are
in the books
that stop mid-sentence.
Why is he dead? And it's one of the most
serious promises he
can make. She will be his translation. Moods
meanwhile.  It's included besides the first
verse. I'm going to finish it.
I promise that, or unless I
die, it'll take another 25 years. Have
fun with that.
How much time do I have left? We still
have half an hour.
[Music]
The great thing about the verse is that the great thing about
this first verse is that of the three
basic threads, what
he did was include the three threads in the first verse.
We have the three basic ones. Wait with that,
baby, mix it up.
I give you permission
to memorize these three best threads.
You want me to reduce with three
basic threads. Quote
the first one. People say that's not it, but there are
21 more verses coming. Then
you say, but everything is included in the first verse.
He called that currently after English.
Switch as best as I can. I'll
explain the last line. The
Tibetan syntax and the English
syntax and the Tibetan are exactly the
opposite. Buy what I'm going to buy.
Here is the essence of the
sixth Buddhism.
Which of the three basics? Learning a
widespread phenomenon. Flow. A
straight line is also called...  The
alternative is lost along a line,
right there was, and in the end is
a gene of the English "th". In the end,
the essence of the noise of the
victorious is and say it's too much.
The yoga teachers let their students suffer. The
path brings all the holy ones.
I have, I translated that 20 years ago
and have always only
used the masculine form. We are the
children of the Bundesliga. May I? I
think I have the name. You are the one who was made up
that you are a
ball pit of Buddhists, and that is
us. The individual places for the DD
citizenship want to reach. There is
still the apprenticeship, the
understanding of the teachers. The pen of the
last line is about the pen. If
you have someone's pen explained correctly, have
you then and entered the ocean and
crossed the river and will possibly
reach freedom? The
apprenticeship is therefore already mentioned in the
third line, but I will
not.
I will now explain the great points.
The first line is the essence of
all Buddhist teachings, and he
now wants to talk about what it does
not contain in the learning—and that is
the same.  The point we
already discussed this morning is not wasting
your time and mental capacity. And so,
this is the topic now,
and in a letter, he always wrote from the cape to
Lama, or everyone except
Islam, Apa, yes, he spoke with some,
and what was his profession? So
Schöppl said
he was a shepherd in the mountains.
He was simply an old shepherd, and
people said he had already
met them,
and that's why they forced him.
Why did you sometimes really
meet them? Did you have a direct
telephone connection to some? Yes,
the old shepherd in dirty clothes. Yes,
I have a direct connection with the
cape. Ask if the truth is true, Sachs.
If I was Apa, I had
two cases. Okay, La Bomba said Japan
asks a question, and he gave all the
difficult questions about apprenticeships.
What is the teacher between
consciousness 6 and 7, and Ab gave
a perfect answer every time, and
they went to the captain's visit. Raging, help from
Munch's scream, and after a
year
It's simply a waste of time that
I'm always here on the mountain where
Grandma and Dad taught me to make direct contact
with some people, and that's why it's said that
she wrote so well about the body,
and later
people said he is already the
teacher, people always know how to
teach me, and I simply decided to teach
the two pages long from the
t-shirt, so light on the
path to enlightenment, this opinion,
now I am a famous teacher, everyone
asks me to teach, and I have found out
the best thing I can
teach is a short run,
that is always on the body, after many
years of teaching, the trade,
the best thing that helps the students, or
where everything is contained, it's a small
country, was understood,
that is the next part of the class, a
single lecture on the stages to
enlightenment, includes all
Buddhist teachings contained in this
world,
I will try
to get these from the left and also focus on the jewel of the
topic, 11 and 12 years, and he says these
books are education complete,
they do not have the complete, certainly
not ideas themselves  The open titles, they
call that where her husband, for example, had
the open learning content, and the other
had secret learning, not yet, but in the
lab, both are included,
and if you think about it, it's
the better opposite, he says, and in the
next 25 minutes, you could sleep with your eyes open
and simply not in
this way and this way, and there are other
ways and drinking,
then you can read and understand all the other books by
Butter. That is the
key that made all the books understandable,
so study in their own way,
and that helps you with the other 17
courses, and so reinforced that the Islam
minister unfortunately closed all the others from
Wolverine, from the dress,
going from here to there, but what is now of what comes after,
yes, everything out there, all
300 so far are in this little mouth, keep
them all in this little one. If you
want to study for three years in parallel, yes,
or, and that is also how it is, first learn LA Bremen
Castro, the key to all doors,
and if you want to go with that, then
you will find that everything in this
new content, from my personal
experience, I have 35 pages, and then
it happened.
I simply want to tell you the  The idea of
selling it by heart, in
English or Chinese, Spanish, it doesn't
matter which language
Pimco should be in,
but what cool thing happens then is
Hamburg when Storting has
Opel countries, it's out when the shine, then
this bull speaks to
you all day in your mind,
strange things happen,
Jean Gabin speaks in a mind
all day or May turn,
I thought of it as breakfast,
how simply appear in your head,
we had this morning, we spoke in
English, it's called when it's the little
snippets, the three basic things, that
can, they come, a breath of
your mind, when you're with your
girlfriend, what then said to the body, the
path from my personal,
someone told me that, but I told
myself that happened, so I love it,
I believe that at one point you
learn well by heart, then
the race changes live,
I don't want to brag now, but I
think I get smarter every year, I don't know
what stops and when I
start to forget things, there's
a drama that when you
memorize these books, then analyzes
Something's wrong with his battery and it keeps getting
higher and that's cool
then you can be a better
businessman his skills
increase when jets and can use it to make
rock 'n' roll be for
this good morning I think
half-and-half is a good balance 50%
roll and 50 percent discount
because my mind tomorrow that's my
suggestion
[Music]
he sells that corresponds but the
belief
then repeated what we've already
learned today and he has the laptop or that
's the proof
very interesting traditionally
after a strong wave of questions the
completion of wisdom does
not refer to school but to the
books the 5000 weres the 8000 fans and
let the Yaman Schneider so that one is
also called the 300 Nazi
and then it gets less and less and
less was getting what is the
shortest hunter type a chip
that means if you want to show off
I have a super memorized
impress time
you have to tell him that's all
and he quotes and the completion of
wisdom and he says  This is the source
for the word national budgets. Before you, it
is this completion, nothing else that is
shared by all victorious ones, which is
glad to the past, present, and future that we traveled. This
is the la boum. This is a quote. House
of the completion of wisdom. There
are three things you can do. With the
latter, you can
sleep in or grin. Very convenient,
as if the second order is always
with the crane. The third order is that he
only wakes up when Keller says it's
worth 100 dollars.
What was it again for the 100
dollars?
I forgot. Yes, yes, I know. I
said it with a highest short. Now a question: that cowboys, SWB cowboys
with the pistols.
I am ready. The completion of the
wisdom of the church is in them.
Really, the lampre. They hold us.
Allegedly, they choose the sport.
Islam.
It is said that they are the source. Are
they really being now because the
elements are contained? If so, then
we wouldn't.
They go. There is an even better
answer. There is
definitely a country that is
not in the  The completion of wisdom,
what is the completion, praying would be
the topic very open because wisdom
is empty and there is one person, but the
feeling is usually
not explicitly addressed. Talk about
the two lovers in the command. We
often ask what the obvious
topic is and what goes underneath.
So if you have a debate,
you can deny the questions.
The completion of wisdom, both
strands in Reims, majority, and you can't
lose, then you say love
is not exclusively addressed. If he
uses this logic, you can still turn it with your partner. So to the body, PokerStars
dad tells us that
for the country, the completion of
wisdom is thus refuted again. You,
the statement that lamps were invented by the clubs,
and then it continues. Do
n't waste time.
The glass flower doesn't do any nonsense with
a ghost, and the one quoted here
says Johann Dieter, I think. Yes, that's
a big name. The dead end, not the
first, but the most famous. 200 years ago,
before buying
during Genghis Khan's time.  Khan, I think I
read that I fit. If you buy a horse
or a car, save money, talk to me.
I think I'll buy a car. What was your
experience? Yes, it was quite good, and I had one
too.
But don't buy a radio or a Chevrolet.
You catch people. Is the
2009/10 model as good as 2000? You
just don't want the wrong car. Now,
also buying an apartment, renting. Is there a
café? Is it that people who have been
in the Diana
business for 20 years...? But people still call me again
to compensate with a diamond
as long as it is... And you
can get a good one from Amazon, not from the
wrong one.
So, if someone could spend a lot,
then ask many people. But hypo
at 53...
But when people buy, they take
everything like a hungry person. Everything
they see on the street, they eat. And
then you say, how high does it take the
dogs? Does it cost to design or result in
an inauguration? You go, there's a $35 one,
and it should have such a weight
before not seven years, and the lynx is
simply down. You ask if it...  Pain, and that's why it will be strange,
we care
more about cars and names, you're in
weird meditation classes and you don't ask,
and maybe
I'll have eaten diving sometime, JK, that's it,
and then they still
offered real chocolate, talking, and
I took a big bite, and that was the
motto, chocolate for the mouse, I'm so
sorry, or what, the appeal, CDA cake,
I'll catch you, says Japan, the
deed doesn't speak for everything, and then you
come, then he quotes several more
email addresses, interesting guy, think
is important to me, the meal, the most
famous, me, NCTB, everyone says that
every wheel has to search, he was the most
famous media in Tibet, helps stock markets,
songs, and his 100,000 liters is a
bad translation of the perpetrator because it's
not 100,000, it's just a
collection, Thyssen collection of poems, that's what
the handball arena calls, is why
he's the most famous, meditating, he
only started meditating when he
already had ten years ago, according to the
average age today would be  He says
he was 40 when he did his big retreats, so
few people currently say
that old to start meditating. Oh, so start
or operate like that. You can
teach tricks to an old dog;
it's always possible to start something. Do
n't tell me you're too old to start
meditating. Villa DPA, the
most famous meditator of all time, was 50
before he started initiating
and writing,
and he says, "I told you about
his beliefs, normal activity,
and so I did too, over 6 million, now it's starting."
But the point was, this is
about the data domain, and I know it fits
then if you don't follow the
advice that's passed from ear
to ear. The place
was the pump, that's the plan.
It's like with the hip hop song; then
you can sit here in a cave,
but you can meditate,
but you just disappear. Your time...
who says that's the biggest cave
meditation of all time? So do
n't waste your time if you're
not meditating in a good line, an
authentic step. If it's not a real
teaching, then...  Don't waste your
time. I was in the Himalayan heights.
I'm here, Himalayan cave master. I still
have six minutes and I'm going to
use them.
Yes, the first homework question. I wo
n't be able to finish all the homework tonight,
and if you don't have any homework tomorrow,
you need to relax. I'm
really sorry. The ability of a book
or practically all of them. If
someone tries to
sell you a practice, I have these three
qualities. Then don't waste
your time with it. Don't ruin the
class. It should be emptied of Kodak. Why? Why
is that better?
He knows you're leaving the book today.
When they wrote the book,
he read your mind. When he
had the northern life, number two, that's
important. Of the whole building, I don't
want to say anything about the Buddhist
lineage. I was
raised Christian.  The head chef of
Princeton is Mimi Kristin Star, and
a university degree refers to
switching to Christian studies. I
really wanted that, and
I was sent to a seminary, and
then I went to India. I never came back,
but that's another
story. The coasts in Christianity, following
trends further back, so you have to learn it in Greek,
Latin.
I studied Greek in Oxford,
in the city of Oxford. No, it
wasn't at Oxford University.
The ideas, I think, essential studies, the
further back you go, and so Rainer
and Buddhist studies, the great
you came. The
more you drank, a few bankers, the more
Rainer it is. That's very interesting. If
you really want to understand this, go
back, it comes to the body of Jean-Claude
Juncker, or it became a compass
comedy murder because they made it clearer, you
see more clearly, clearer, won
easily, to read more easily, is responsible,
and he would be very disappointed if he read the
completion of wisdom, second race,
you  You couldn't
understand anything, do
n't waste your time on disco, that
's the last thing we ever are to translate
our school except to trust the Lord,
but if you publish the completion of
wisdom about collections,
nobody will understand it, you need
that generation more explanations where it can be
so completely, can you go to China, no
more students from the North in multimedia,
Kamalla China where these 1300 years have not been
taught, so be it, I know,
you can't read it,
June to have, you need, you need
punks, and you need, yes, I started to
mark, and that can go
back a generation, so it is exactly the
opposite of Christian studies,
the more years pass, the
better the planning becomes, the clearer
the presentation,
that is really more used origins,
which, so if a saturation
started, then media to the Capitol,
after 30 years, do you understand, session came,
because otherwise you understand it, made, do it
backwards, so industry table in
this tradition, solutions, as the years
passed, it became pure and clear,
and that is a second piece of advice, which
books  Books should be read about this, which has gone through
the process of purification by
the Greek generations.
His body is
until this, that is the second suggestion.
The first love remains with the things
spoken about the Buddha, but study
it over a sum about a love that
every generation has. It should be made longer.
The presentation
that tormented us, people into the valley. Yes, of
course, Chandra Kelti's explanation was
clear at the time, and sadism.
People are getting dumber and dumber just because we have the
airplanes. Don't think
that the ancient Romans were like that; they had
whole books from
Dillinger back then. We can do that today.
Comments were to be clear for you. Do
n't be yourself. That explanations were clear
for you. Don't talk, but we need this.
This is the second one. Through the
generations that made it accessible to you,
forget how the
relationship between accurate and
accessible works.
But otherwise, you make the lack of
chocolate cake more aesthetically
accessible. As a teacher, a
representation is accessible. Modern,
here you can. Can you tell me by tomorrow? Report from
Taiwan. Is it possible tomorrow evening?
She has it, but not fundamentally. Is that the
last of the
can?  Already booked, not to
what they not only protons Peru and there
what is not progressing, what is accessible
and what was passed on through one,
and it should have been applied by successful people
and were successful in it, so
if someone else has practiced it
and hasn't seen the apprenticeship,
anyone who has studied tantra,
macho and June, or people from face to face, has
anyone trusted them, and the
answer is Aldi types, have they
met it,
it should rather have their own, they want it,
then the next generation
continues, we the two parts of
sweat,
it should convey what they should experience,
they should have passed it on to those who have built it,
spiritual mother had Lopatka, had
a breakdown, had his own,
it happened on it, they study with them, there is
a true story,
so we don't hand it in tomorrow,
all the information is in the trade, the
homework questions, what are the three
qualities of a good Buddhist,
Regis, mother taught it, number two,
it would make him purer over time, clearer,
someone asked me, yoga situation,
it has become clear that the fourth
chapter will eventually be added to someone else,
and so it is in many  spiritual
books, but in Buddhism it's not
Buddhism, people don't, and
the third thing would be by Saturday, foresters' success
stories should be known,
understood, that
only includes the castle throw, could that be
a good political book, and
we'll continue with that tomorrow, law firm, several
Demir use, we will finish class 4, I gave a little
vacation yesterday,
I tried to go slowly,
so we will now concentrate on the homework again,
you can read it yourself, I think it
's the longest reading because I
simply gave my old translations that
I already had publicly
in the course, and it's
a long reading, the others did
n't have too long,
we always reach the 400 verses of Michael,
and that means he was an
hourly pace, or he brings the book
about love, written
around 400 AD, he wrote every
coast and in this highly written,
we have had a definition of a teacher,
and now I want to experience the
definition of a study, those are the
characteristics of a studio, that's also
in the store shelf, collective, what is there  It
is described what a
qualified teacher is, and then one is allowed to say
what a
qualified teacher is. It's already running, solving problems, and there's
a nice list of a
student's qualities.
I think it's the shortest. There are
many other lists that are very slow.
The goal of ESI 11 is to present things
within ten classes.
The complete blood is what, so that's why
we can't have a
boring sun. That's what the corner is called, but also
knows as well as former, the former
Arno Lang, free,
so not in the corner, soon parked
in the corner. To take it means open, see
you don't go position.
That means you don't take any behavior
before you get into the classics, into the tumble. A
good student in the district with roles
comes with an open, horny attitude
to the presentation. It means that they are all
here now,
but they have, they are, they have no
prejudices about, of course,
they go into the class, have greetings, new
idea, so they go into class 3a,
says, but don't manipulate immediately,
but ask, plan a lot for witnesses
and try  to fit these interests,
you were already there, you know how Adobe people
gold is good, the Creation Center Rimini's, it's half past
two, actions and three
meanings, nettle, cut it and
arrows it, burn it, cut it and
arrows it, that which people, what, what, like
tests for new information from,
we had them in China, soft power,
recently, series, very good, contradicts,
contradicts something that
the teacher already said before, so if he, if
he says on Monday there is
meat and last Friday there is no
condition, contradicts that I, what is
the first race, travels, fit, are a
personal experience, for example, yes,
if I eat meat I am fine, what is the
second, cutting logic,
use your logo, his common
sense, does it make sense, this
logic, is it logical, so, the tenant's dose,
these are the three tests for the
study,
a student is initially ideas into the
room and a cost reduction is, but they
check, comment on everything,
they check everything, now that is also the
second quality, a high IQ, what
a gem  spiritual when I started the SP
politicians after that
first course, I think we had five
or six students.
I handed out the homework, and
I think that was the first time
anyone ever did a Nordic
to cancel bleep, and I tried. There are
two types:
they always get 100s, but the
unfriendly ones are all stars. The teacher who gets the
highest grade will be them, and/or
teachers, but they are reducing the
people who are not good so much as the
students, and then there are the 90s or
90s. They weren't number 1 at home,
but it's
the number 1 who sees being nice to other
people, purely a category, and so is an ace.
I think these are two
different ones. In America,
we are good at writing. I was the best
student every year in Arizona.
There is an intelligent one to
refer to the tests, but there are also always
real internet or or,
and we are talking about the second
type of spiritually advanced
test in math. High school diploma, 0 dollars,
okay, I'll ask to borrow money, or not?
Daisy Duck series classes sometimes  Do
they cry in class? Oh, there was when
you get goosebumps.
You speak of superiority and sometimes
critically.
He had the clotheslines. A single one
means when you have a high school
ritual of your own hatred and someone starts
talking about teachers,
then goosebumps run down their back
and then you also see them start to think again.
So try to
hide the onion in your pocket and
start changing the leg in class.
[Music]
Hygienic models. Angeles has made me.
According to the recipe from Genoa, the
third quality was how she is a great vision.
Someone who is from Baumberger illegally from
Mountain.
You can stand on the Hellenfelder.
It's about us here, a world, and there are
stars. Tour tips soon. Forums.
It is Ramos Pepe. Not just two by
three centimeters. Ears. Manage cities. There are
copied stars on
transmitters and thinks big, including costs. Sky
established for the traffic light cards. Ski
jumping over the sky.
That simply means professors. Everyone with
barrier training. We have the feeling
That if version rules go well then
it will spread quickly,
never organized before, we will
organize it now, it had no vision
here at the front,
because Juve was never between the 1st,
that is, the great vision in spirit,
won, you want to understand it now, every
person on these channels,
and again, and that means my
person is welcome to drive, forms, that is,
everyone is a Tibetan Pohl,
it will mean that people start to
apply the four steps, the ideas
on the old and sick, very nice that
you could be successful, are to
rise, get and on cash or the
audience drove all over the world and
people forget who started it,
that is probably a personal,
I want that, and I also want to
change the culture on other planets,
and I want everyone to forget, thus
it started, Storageworks, who invented it,
if I ask at the end, who has a
public library,
most, you must have been very, very
rich back then to know a book because
we were copied by hand,
only the rich people had books and
they didn't deliver them, but
Visp Potter book  Citizens find and he
said all rich people put their books
in a building and eventually lose track of
how they are borrowed. I believe there are
public libraries everywhere in the world
and you can
borrow books, and we have forgotten who had
the idea when we want to be spiritual
Benjamin Friese. Where is his picture
on the 100 dollar bill, not on the one
dollar bill? As professionals,
that is proof that he was really good.